ANDREW ZAMBAZOS

- **♀** Palmerston North, New Zealand
- ☑ andrewzambazos@gmail.com
- **** +64274738940
- https://www.andrewzambazos.com

OBJECTIVE

I'm looking for part-time work in the role of Game Designer in the arts and media industry.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Passionate Game Designer with 9 years of experience with years of experience in Unreal Engine, Unity, Godot, and the Bethesda Creation Engine. My goals in my career are to work at a AAA game studio helping out design the next award winning game.

WORK HISTORY

Olympus Studios

Remotely, New Zealand Nov 2022 - Present

Fallout Wastelands

Remotely, New Zealand Jun 2021 - Present

Studio Lead / Producer

I am currently a Producer and lead of world design at Olympus Studios currently working on a new IP and

unique game Elysium that is being built in Unreal Engine 5 and has an innovative story and world design with a unique design.

Lead Designer

I am Lead Designer on the fallout mod "Fallout: Wastelands" where I coordinate a team of level designers to create a immersive and interesting world space and interiors in the Fallout world. I helped in

planning and designing the mod from a design standpoint along with writers and artists.

• Overseeing a design department

QUALIFICATIONS

Awatapu College

Palmerston North, New Zealand Present

NCEA Level 1

- Mathematics Internal Achieved With Merit
- Hard Materials Woodwork Achieved With Merit
- Media Studies Achieved With Merit

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Unreal Engine (Blueprints)
- C++
- Bethesda Creation Engine
- Javascript
- Git

- Unity
- C#
- Java
- Python

PERSONAL SKILLS

BFlat Tuba

I have been playing the Bflat tuba for almost 2 years

Tenor / Baritone Saxophone

I have been playing the Saxophone for 3 years

Radio Presenting

I host a radio show on Manawatu Peoples Radio

COMMUNITY & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

New Zealand National Secondary Schools Brass Band

Nelson, New Zealand Oct 2024 - Oct 2024

Manawatu Sinfonia

Palmerston North, New Zealand Sep 2024 - Present

Manawatu Youth Orchestra

Palmerston North, New Zealand Jul 2024 - Present

Awatapu Jazz Band

Palmerston North, New Zealand Aug 2022 - Present

Palmerston North Brass Band

Palmerston North, New Zealand Apr 2022 - Present I successfully auditioned and got into the National Secondary Schools Brass Band of New Zealand on BFlat Bass

I play BFlat Bass in the Manawatu Youth Orchestra

I play the Double B Flat Tuba in the Palmerston North Brass Band where I have played in a number of

including "A Concert of Two Halves" and a joined concert with Fielding Brass Band

INTERESTS

- Game Development
- Video Games
- Game Modding

- Music
- Digital Art

REFEREES

Referees available on request.